<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Ritsu TL | Ritsu TL</title>
        <link>https://ritsu.dev/</link>
        <description>Ritsu TL | Ritsu TL</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><atom:link href="https://ritsu.dev/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
                <title>Wns</title>
                <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/</guid>
                <description></description>
            </item><item>
                <title>About</title>
                <link>https://ritsu.dev/about/</link>
                <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://ritsu.dev/about/</guid>
                <description></description>
            </item><item>
                <title>Cookie Policy</title>
                <link>https://ritsu.dev/cookie-policy/</link>
                <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://ritsu.dev/cookie-policy/</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;This policy describes how Ritsu TL uses cookies on &lt;a href=&#34;https://ritsu.dev&#34;&gt;https://ritsu.dev&lt;/a&gt; (the “Site”). We recommend that you also consult our Privacy Policy for additional information on how we collect and use information collected from visitors to the Site. Your continued use of the Site after that will signify your acceptance of this policy. We may modify this Agreement without notifying you, so please check back often for updates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By using the Site, you agree that we can use the cookies described in this Cookie Policy. You can stop cookies by changing the settings in your browser (more information on how to do this is provided below).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-are-cookies&#34;&gt;WHAT ARE COOKIES?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cookies are text files, containing small amounts of information, which are downloaded to your browsing device (such as a computer or smartphone) when you visit a website. Cookies can be recognized by the website that downloaded them — or other websites that use the same cookies. This helps websites know if the browsing device has visited them before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-are-cookies-used-for&#34;&gt;WHAT ARE COOKIES USED FOR?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cookies do lots of different jobs, like helping us understand how the Site is being used, letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improving your browsing experience. Cookies can also help ensure marketing you see online is more relevant to you and your interests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-types-of-cookies-does-ritsu-tl-use&#34;&gt;WHAT TYPES OF COOKIES DOES RITSU TL USE?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The type of cookies used on most websites can generally be put into one of six categories: Strictly Necessary, Performance, Functionality, Flash, Tailored Content and Targeting. In order to provide you with the best browsing experience, Ritsu TL uses all of these categories on the Site. You can find out more about each cookie category in the sections below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strictly Necessary Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These cookies are essential, as they enable you to move around the Site and use its features, such as accessing secure areas. Without these cookies, some services you have asked for such as payment submission can’t be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These cookies collect information about how you use the Site, for example which pages you go to most often and if you get error messages from certain pages. These cookies don’t gather information that identifies you. All information these cookies collect is anonymous and is only used to improve how the Site works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Functionality Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These cookies allow the Site to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you’re in). For instance, the Site uses functionality cookies to remember your language preference. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you’ve made to text size, font and other parts of pages that you can customize. They may also be used to provide services you’ve asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymous and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flash Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may, in certain circumstances, use Adobe Flash Player to deliver special content, such as video clips or animation. To improve your user experience, Local Shared Objects (commonly known as “Flash cookies”) are employed to provide functions such as remembering your settings and preferences. Flash cookies are stored on your device, but they are managed through an interface different from the one provided by your web browser. This means it is not possible to manage Flash cookies through your browser in the same way you would normally manage cookies. Instead, you can access your Flash management tools from Adobe’s website at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html&#34;&gt;http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tailored Content Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tailored content cookies help the Site provide enhanced features and display content in a way that is relevant to you. These cookies help the Site determine what information to show you based on how you have used the Site previously. These cookies do not track your browsing activity on other websites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Targeting Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These cookies are used to deliver advertisements that are more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign. They remember that you have visited a website and this information may be shared with other organizations such as advertisers. This means after you have been to the Site you may see some advertisements about our services elsewhere on the Internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-long-will-cookies-stay-on-my-browsing-device&#34;&gt;HOW LONG WILL COOKIES STAY ON MY BROWSING DEVICE?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The length of time a cookie will stay on your browsing device depends on whether it is a “persistent” or “session” cookie. Session cookies will only stay on your device until you stop browsing. Persistent cookies stay on your browsing device until they expire or are deleted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;first-and-third-party-cookies&#34;&gt;FIRST AND THIRD PARTY COOKIES&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First party cookies are cookies that belong to us, while third party cookies are cookies that another party places on your browsing device through our Site. For example, Facebook will place a cookie on your browsing device if you click on the Facebook link when browsing the Site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-control-and-delete-cookies-through-your-browser&#34;&gt;HOW TO CONTROL AND DELETE COOKIES THROUGH YOUR BROWSER&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The browser you are using to view the Site can enable, disable or delete cookies. To do this, follow the instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the “Help,” “Tools” or “Edit” facility). Please note that if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain parts of the Site for example applying for a job or posting a job. Other parts of the Site may also not work properly. You can find out more information about how to change your browser cookie settings at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.allaboutcookies.org&#34;&gt;www.allaboutcookies.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;contact-us&#34;&gt;CONTACT US&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about this Cookie Policy, you may contact us using the information below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ritsu &lt;a href=&#34;&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreffer&#34;&gt;dot&lt;/a&gt;
 dev &lt;a href=&#34;&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreffer&#34;&gt;at&lt;/a&gt;
 gmail &lt;a href=&#34;&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreffer&#34;&gt;dot&lt;/a&gt;
 com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
            </item><item>
                <title>Disclaimer</title>
                <link>https://ritsu.dev/disclaimer/</link>
                <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://ritsu.dev/disclaimer/</guid>
                <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no guarantee the translations are 100% correct.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The translations on this website are licensed under &lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreffer&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further, &lt;strong&gt;Ritsu TL&lt;/strong&gt; does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its website or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ritsu TL&lt;/strong&gt; may revise these disclaimer for its website at any time without notice. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these disclaimer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
            </item><item>
                <title>Indexes</title>
                <link>https://ritsu.dev/index/</link>
                <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://ritsu.dev/index/</guid>
                <description></description>
            </item><item>
                <title>Privacy Policy</title>
                <link>https://ritsu.dev/privacy-policy/</link>
                <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://ritsu.dev/privacy-policy/</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Ritsu TL (&amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;we&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;us&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;our&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot;) respects the privacy of our users (&amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;user&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;you&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot;). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our website &lt;a href=&#34;https://ristu.dev&#34;&gt;https://ristu.dev&lt;/a&gt;, including any other media form, media channel, mobile website, or mobile application related or connected thereto (collectively, the &amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;Site&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot;). Please read this privacy policy carefully. If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, please do not access the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We will alert you about any changes by updating the &amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;Last Updated&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;rdquo; date of this Privacy Policy. Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting the updated Privacy Policy on the Site, and you waive the right to receive specific notice of each such change or modification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted the changes in any revised Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Site after the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;information-collection&#34;&gt;INFORMATION COLLECTION&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may collect information about you in a variety of ways. The information we may collect on the Site may include, but is not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personal Data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personally identifiable information, such as your name, shipping address, email address, and telephone number, and demographic information, such as your age, gender, hometown, and interests, that you voluntarily give to us when you register with the Site or when you choose to participate in various activities related to the Site, such as online chat and message boards. You are under no obligation to provide us with personal information of any kind, however your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features of the Site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Derivative Data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Information our servers automatically collect when you access the Site, such as your IP address, your browser type, your operating system, your access times, and the pages you have viewed directly before and after accessing the Site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data From Social Networks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;User information from social networking sites, such as &lt;em&gt;Facebook&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Instagram&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Pinterest&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Twitter&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Reddit&lt;/em&gt;, and others, including your name, your social network username, location, gender, birth date, email address, profile picture, and public data for contacts, if you connect your account to such social networks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mobile Device Data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Device information, such as your mobile device ID, model, and manufacturer, and information about the location of your device, if you access the Site from a mobile device.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third-Party Data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Information from third parties, such as personal information or network friends, if you connect your account to the third party and grant the Site permission to access this information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data From Contests, Giveaways, and Surveys&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal and other information you may provide when entering contests or giveaways and/or responding to surveys.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;use-of-you-information&#34;&gt;USE OF YOU INFORMATION&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having accurate information about you permits us to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. Specifically, we may use information collected about you via the Site to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Administer sweepstakes, promotions, and contests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist law enforcement and respond to subpoena.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compile anonymous statistical data and analysis for use internally or with third parties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and manage your account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deliver targeted advertising, coupons, newsletters, and other information regarding promotions and the Site to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email you regarding your account or order.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enable user-to-user communications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, and other transactions related to the Site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate a personal profile about you to make future visits to the Site more personalized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increase the efficiency and operation of the Site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor and analyze usage and trends to improve your experience with the Site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notify you of updates to the Site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Offer new products, services, and/or recommendations to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform other business activities as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft, and protect against criminal activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Process payments and refunds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Request feedback and contact you about your use of the Site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respond to product and customer service requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send you a newsletter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;disclosure-of-your-information&#34;&gt;DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may share information we have collected about you in certain situations. Your information may be disclosed as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By Law or to Protect Rights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If we believe the release of information about you is necessary to respond to legal process, to investigate or remedy potential violations of our policies, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others, we may share your information as permitted or required by any applicable law, rule, or regulation. This includes exchanging information with other entities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third-Party Service Providers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may share your information with third parties that perform services for us or on our behalf, including payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service, and marketing assistance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marketing Communications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With your consent, or with an opportunity for you to withdraw consent, we may share your information with third parties for marketing purposes, as permitted by law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interactions with Other Users&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you interact with other users of the Site, those users may see your name, profile photo, and descriptions of your activity, including sending invitations to other users, chatting with other users, liking posts, following blogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Online Postings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you post comments, contributions or other content to the Site, your posts may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside the Site in perpetuity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third-Party Advertisers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site. These companies may use information about your visits to the Site and other websites that are contained in web cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Affiliates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include our parent company and any subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Business Partners&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products, services or promotions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Third Parties&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may share your information with advertisers and investors for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. We may also share your information with such third parties for marketing purposes, as permitted by law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sale or Bankruptcy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If we reorganize or sell all or a portion of our assets, undergo a merger, or are acquired by another entity, we may transfer your information to the successor entity. If we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, your information would be an asset transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that the transferee may decline honor commitments we made in this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are not responsible for the actions of third parties with whom you share personal or sensitive data, and we have no authority to manage or control third-party solicitations. If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tracking-technologies&#34;&gt;TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cookies and Web Beacons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels, and other tracking technologies on the Site to help customize the Site and improve your experience. When you access the Site, your personal information is not collected through the use of tracking technology. Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. You can remove or reject cookies, but be aware that such action could affect the availability and functionality of the Site. You may not decline web beacons. However, they can be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or by modifying your web browser’s settings to notify you each time a cookie is tendered, permitting you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels, and other tracking technologies on the Site to help customize the Site and improve your experience. For more information on how we use cookies, please refer to our &lt;a href=&#34;https://ritsu.dev/cookie-policy&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreffer&#34;&gt;Cookie Policy&lt;/a&gt;
 posted on the Site, which is incorporated into this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you agree to be bound by our Cookie Policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Internet-Based Advertising&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, we may use third-party software to serve ads on the Site, implement email marketing campaigns, and manage other interactive marketing initiatives. This third-party software may use cookies or similar tracking technology to help manage and optimize your online experience with us. For more information about opting-out of interest-based ads, visit the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool or Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Tool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Website Analytics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may also partner with selected third-party vendors, such as &lt;em&gt;Adobe Analytics&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Cloudfare&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Crazy Egg&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Flurry Analytics&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/em&gt;, and others, to allow tracking technologies and remarketing services on the Site through the use of first party cookies and third-party cookies, to, among other things, analyze and track users’ use of the Site, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. By accessing the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by these third-party vendors. You are encouraged to review their privacy policy and contact them directly for responses to your questions. We do not transfer personal information to these third-party vendors. However, if you do not want any information to be collected and used by tracking technologies, you can visit the third-party vendor or the &lt;strong&gt;Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Tool&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should be aware that getting a new computer, installing a new browser, upgrading an existing browser, or erasing or otherwise altering your browser’s cookies files may also clear certain opt-out cookies, plug-ins, or settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;third-party-websites&#34;&gt;THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Site may contain links to third-party websites and applications of interest, including advertisements and external services, that are not affiliated with us. Once you have used these links to leave the Site, any information you provide to these third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of your information. Before visiting and providing any information to any third-party websites, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of the third party responsible for that website, and should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect the privacy of your information. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other sites, services or applications that may be linked to or from the Site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;security-of-your-information&#34;&gt;SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We use administrative, technical, and physical security measures to help protect your personal information. While we have taken reasonable steps to secure the personal information you provide to us, please be aware that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse. Any information disclosed online is vulnerable to interception and misuse by unauthorized parties. Therefore, we cannot guarantee complete security if you provide personal information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;policy-for-children&#34;&gt;POLICY FOR CHILDREN&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Site does not address anyone under the age of 18 (&amp;ldquo;Children&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;controls-for-do-not-track-features&#34;&gt;CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this Privacy Policy. Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. If you set the DNT signal on your browser, we will respond to such DNT browser signals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;options-regarding-your-information&#34;&gt;OPTIONS REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Account Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may at any time review or change the information in your account or terminate your account by:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logging into your account settings and updating your account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contacting us using the contact information provided below&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with legal requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Emails and Communications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from us, you may opt-out by:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Noting your preferences at the time you register your account with the Site [or our mobile application].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logging into your account settings and updating your preferences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contacting us using the contact information provided below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;contact-us&#34;&gt;CONTACT US&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us using the information below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ritsu &lt;a href=&#34;&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreffer&#34;&gt;dot&lt;/a&gt;
 dev &lt;a href=&#34;&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreffer&#34;&gt;at&lt;/a&gt;
 gmail &lt;a href=&#34;&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreffer&#34;&gt;dot&lt;/a&gt;
 com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
            </item><item>
                <title>Terms of Service</title>
                <link>https://ritsu.dev/terms-of-service/</link>
                <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://ritsu.dev/terms-of-service/</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Ritsu TL Terms of Service&lt;/strong&gt; is comprised of the following agreements:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ritsu.dev/disclaimer&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreffer&#34;&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ritsu.dev/cookie-policy&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreffer&#34;&gt;Cookie Policy&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ritsu.dev/privacy-policy&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreffer&#34;&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
            </item></channel>
</rss>
