<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wns on Ritsu TL</title>
    <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wns on Ritsu TL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ritsu.dev/wn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c25-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c25-2/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps convinced by Kaburagi-san&amp;rsquo;s explanation, Detective Kumano didn&amp;rsquo;t pursue the matter with the students further. Instead, he leaned forward slightly with his elbow on the counter.
&amp;ldquo;We are looking for these three. Code named; Time Lady, Burning Gal, and Freezing Knight.&amp;rdquo;
The rough-looking Detective Kumano said three names you&amp;rsquo;d expect to find in American comics while showing me pictures of three men in black. I understand he&amp;rsquo;s being serious. However, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but find this situation slightly funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c25-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c25-1/</guid>
      <description>Shortly after she started her hunt for the traitor, Touka-chan recounted everything to Shouta-kun and roped him in as her ally. Thanks to that, the scene of betrayal event I had planned for Shouta-kun went up in smoke.
I wondered if Touka-chan suspected Shouta-kun to be the traitor, but from what I gathered after eavesdropping on them, it seems for Touka-chan, Shouta-kun is someone who could never pull off something as clever as the &amp;lsquo;red herring&amp;rsquo; trick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c24-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 12:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c24-1/</guid>
      <description>It was time for the betrayal event featuring Baba. It would start with the disappearance of some PSI drives.
Tricked by the wicked Demon King who was allegedly manipulating the World&amp;rsquo;s Darkness, Baba would hand over a couple of PSI Drives and their blueprints (she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t actually hand it over), and leak Amaterasu&amp;rsquo;s classified information (no, she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t leak anything either).
The students would fortuitously notice some PSI drive were missing and report it to Kaburagi-san.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret Organization</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/index/</guid>
      <description>Author : 黒留ハガネ | Kurodome Hagane Raw: 世界の闇と戦う秘密結社が無いから作った（半ギレ） Novel Updates: There Was No Secret Organization to Fight the World’s Darkness so I Made One (In Exasperation) Description The protagonist wakes up to a superpower one day, out</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c24-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c24-2/</guid>
      <description>It is widely believed that a rumor dies out after 75 days, yet the rumors about the Super Water-Ball Incident remained a hot topic for quite a while. However, even this rumor that made headlines globally started to lose steam once a year had passed. It was only when a feature TV program called &amp;ldquo;One year after the Super Water-Ball Incident&amp;rdquo; started airing, people started recalling that incident. But none</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24 - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c24-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c24-3/</guid>
      <description>I called out to Baito-kun who barely escaped from Touka-chan and was breathing heavily. He rushed into the family restaurant which I had designated as our rendezvous point, disguised in a beard and sunglasses.
&amp;ldquo;Over here, over here. Good work, Baito-kun! Here take some Iced-coffee. Ah, do you even drink iced coffee?&amp;rdquo;
Baito-kun nodded and sat down with a thump in a seat across me and took a sip of iced coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>