<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wns on Ritsu TL</title>
    <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wns on Ritsu TL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ritsu.dev/wn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Arc 2 - Side Story</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/arc2-ss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/arc2-ss/</guid>
      <description>There are three ways to enjoy any event.
First, before the event. You enjoy the anticipation and the tantalizing feeling.
Second, during the event. You get insanely busy, but you love how you want to keep going despite how tiring it gets.
Third, after the event. You look back at the hardships you went through, together with your friends and colleagues and laugh about it.
&amp;ldquo;I honestly feel like the second betrayal was kinda harsh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 30</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c30/</guid>
      <description>Yasuo Yasui never particularly liked celebrating a grown man&amp;rsquo;s birthday. But if his honor and money was on line, then it was a different story.
In a corner seat away from the window in a café not far from Amanoiwato, Yasui reported to his accomplice, who was busy sipping apple juice.
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve pushed a ton of work onto Kuma-san as instructed. He should be stuck at his desk tonight, so he won&amp;rsquo;t get in the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c29-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c29-1/</guid>
      <description>Kaneyama Tech is a metallurgical company headquartered in Adachi, Tokyo. It was founded 4 years ago by its young CEO Kaneo Kaneyama (25). This company which only has 280 employees rakes in 600 million yen in gross revenue with 20 million yen in profits annually. Although it was a new player, it is already counted among one of the most influential and innovative companies.
Since a change in management policy was made two years ago, the company&amp;rsquo;s growth has been on an upswing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c29-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c29-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.
Uh, I mean, what the heck!
Wait! Is someone trying to frame me by fabricating evidence?
Flustered, I looked up from the fabricated evidence, only to find the president glaring at me while declaring in conclusion,
&amp;ldquo;I believe that Sago-san is, uhmm.. in someway deeply involved in the smuggling of the package. This is why I had to call both of you today.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I-I didn’t do it. I’m being framed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 29 - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c29-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c29-3/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;How are you doing, Baba-san? I hope you&amp;rsquo;re not having any trouble.&amp;rdquo;
On the first day of the Golden Week holiday, all the members of the secret organization Amaterasu were gathered in Amanoiwato, raising a lively commotion. Baba-Nyan was sitting in the counter seat next to the wall, dangling her legs carefreely while turning the pages of Dostoevsky’s masterpiece Crime and Punishment. Her eyes continued chasing the words on the page even as she answered Kaburagi half-heartedly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 28</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c28/</guid>
      <description>Caution: Chapter has minimal editing. Detective Kumano&amp;rsquo;s nickname changed from Bear-san to Kuma-san. See notes below.  Kuma-san is a veteran detective who has been involved in a number of cases and has solved quite a few of them. In addition, he has participated in and won numerous athletics and martial arts competitions. As a result, he is well known and is respected by his peers. When he returned to Tokyo MPD with Shouta-kun in tow, he announced to all on-site officers &amp;ldquo;Anything about the World&amp;rsquo;s Darkness or espers, you all inform me first&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c27-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c27-2/</guid>
      <description>Even though, Detective Yasui never intruded, I wondered what was going on there. When I checked on them using [Nenrikin] I saw Baba, who had stopped her crying (acting), suddenly look into the distance, and yell &amp;ldquo;Oh, there&amp;rsquo;s my Mommy!&amp;rdquo; and happily dash off. Detective Gesui let out a tired sigh and saw her off. It seems it went well on her side. Baba had exceptional hearing. She must have understood the situation after listening to the sound of battle and our talk afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 27 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c27-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c27-1/</guid>
      <description>Detective Kumano engaged the World&amp;rsquo;s Darkness in a battle while protecting the unconscious Shouta-kun. But he wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to deal any damage. Or rather, I didn&amp;rsquo;t let him deal any damage.
&amp;ldquo;Gah!&amp;rdquo;
He roared like a wild beast and unleashed a Palm Heel Strike, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t work on the World&amp;rsquo;s Darkness. For a moment, it convulsed, but as if nothing had happened, it raised its jaw-like arm in an attempt to cut off Detective Kumano&amp;rsquo;s neck (not really).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26 - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c26-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c26-3/</guid>
      <description>Shouta-kun easily fell for Detective Kumano&amp;rsquo;s bluff and admitted to what was merely his conjecture. To think that the secret of the Amaterasu would leak out so easily! Maybe, I should praise Detective Kumano for his shrewd approach. If he wasn&amp;rsquo;t a policeman, but an oblivious civilian, I&amp;rsquo;d have used [Nenrikin] to shut him up in order to keep our secret. Alas, it&amp;rsquo;s no use thinking about it anymore.
Now, what to do!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c26-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c26-2/</guid>
      <description>It seems the two detectives have decided to investigate Amanoiwato regardless of how we feel. Since there was no shortage of locations suitable for a stakeout, they chose to spy on Amanoiwato from a room in a nearby building and continuously monitored our entrance. But due to them being so close, we were able to use [Stoprotein] and [Nenrikin] [1]  to read their investigation notes and thus better judge their chances of success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 26 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c26-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c26-1/</guid>
      <description>One of the key results of Baba&amp;rsquo;s months of PSI drive research was the replacement of the fake black box at the wind farm with a real PSI drive. Just attaching the black box-shaped PSI drive to the wind turbine did wonders. The wind turbines produced power 24/7 even without my involvement. However, seeing the black box fall into the into the dark side of labor, the company employees shuddered in terror and they offered their blank paid-leave application to appease the raging god at the wind turbine shrine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c25-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c25-2/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps convinced by Kaburagi-san&amp;rsquo;s explanation, Detective Kumano didn&amp;rsquo;t pursue the matter with the students further. Instead, he leaned forward slightly with his elbow on the counter.
&amp;ldquo;We are looking for these three. Code named; Time Lady, Burning Gal, and Freezing Knight.&amp;rdquo;
The rough-looking Detective Kumano said three names you&amp;rsquo;d expect to find in American comics while showing me pictures of three men in black. I understand he&amp;rsquo;s being serious. However, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but find this situation slightly funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c25-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c25-1/</guid>
      <description>Shortly after she started her hunt for the traitor, Touka-chan recounted everything to Shouta-kun and roped him in as her ally. Thanks to that, the scene of betrayal event I had planned for Shouta-kun went up in smoke.
I wondered if Touka-chan suspected Shouta-kun to be the traitor, but from what I gathered after eavesdropping on them, it seems for Touka-chan, Shouta-kun is someone who could never pull off something as clever as the &amp;lsquo;red herring&amp;rsquo; trick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c24-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 12:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c24-1/</guid>
      <description>It was time for the betrayal event featuring Baba. It would start with the disappearance of some PSI drives.
Tricked by the wicked Demon King who was allegedly manipulating the World&amp;rsquo;s Darkness, Baba would hand over a couple of PSI Drives and their blueprints (she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t actually hand it over), and leak Amaterasu&amp;rsquo;s classified information (no, she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t leak anything either).
The students would fortuitously notice some PSI drive were missing and report it to Kaburagi-san.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret Organization</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/index/</guid>
      <description>Author : 黒留ハガネ | Kurodome Hagane Raw: 世界の闇と戦う秘密結社が無いから作った（半ギレ） Novel Updates: There Was No Secret Organization to Fight the World’s Darkness so I Made One (In Exasperation) Description The protagonist wakes up to a superpower one day, out</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c24-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c24-2/</guid>
      <description>It is widely believed that a rumor dies out after 75 days, yet the rumors about the Super Water-Ball Incident remained a hot topic for quite a while. However, even this rumor that made headlines globally started to lose steam once a year had passed. It was only when a feature TV program called &amp;ldquo;One year after the Super Water-Ball Incident&amp;rdquo; started airing, people started recalling that incident. But none</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24 - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c24-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ritsu.dev/wn/secret-org/c24-3/</guid>
      <description>I called out to Baito-kun who barely escaped from Touka-chan and was breathing heavily. He rushed into the family restaurant which I had designated as our rendezvous point, disguised in a beard and sunglasses.
&amp;ldquo;Over here, over here. Good work, Baito-kun! Here take some Iced-coffee. Ah, do you even drink iced coffee?&amp;rdquo;
Baito-kun nodded and sat down with a thump in a seat across me and took a sip of iced coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>